Mitch Reyes

Full Stack Web Developer - ReactJS, MERN, Python, MongoDB

mitchreyes@gmail.com 808-393-3569 922 Northwest 11th Avenue #109 Portland, Oregon 97209

EDUCATION

Bottega University, Lehi, UT (online)— Full Stack Web **Development Course**

01/2020 - 11/2021

- Advanced front-end web development using ReactJS
- HTML/CSS 4/Javascript foundation
- Database functions (Mongo/SQL) Intro to Python and Python Software development

University of Portland, Portland, OR — BBA - Finance

08/2013 - 05/2017

Bachelor's degree in Business Administration – Finance

EXPERIENCE

TEC Equipment, Portland, OR— Flooring Administrator

03/2019 - 04/2021

- Managed all flooring debt lines between TEC Equipment and partnered banks (Wells Fargo and Bank of America)
- Administered the flooring process of internal requests from all TEC branches and administered the flow between the branch. Accounts Payable, and the bank
- Ensured all flooring requests were paid in a timely manner and each unit that was paid for was floored on the bank flooring line within a reasonable amount of time
- Reconciled bank statements with internal accounting sheets to ensure flooring and inventory accounting was identical with bank balance
- Managed and created flooring interest reports for internal analysis and review

NAVEX Global, Lake Oswego, OR— Accounts Receivable Analyst

02/2018 - 02/2019

- Reconciliation and invoicing based on new and existing agreements
- Manage client accounts by analyzing contracts and resolving any client concerns/questions
- Cash posting and bank reconciliation/work with GL team
- Collection responsibilities emails, calling, dunning actions

Coding Languages and Stacks

- ReactJS (React Redux, React Hooks, Axios)
- MERN stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS)
- Javascript
- CSS 4 and SCSS
- Python
- SQL and NOSQL (MongoDB mostly)
- HTML 5

Professional Summary

I graduated with a Bachelor's degree in Finance from the University of Portland and have 4 years of work experience in corporate accounting.

I am currently switching my career path to become a full-stack web developer primarily through an education from Bottega (bottega.tech).

The main coding languages I have learned are Javascript (ReactJS, NodeJS, EnvisionJS), CSS 4/SCSS, Python, MongoDB, and HTML 5.

Github



https://github.com/Mitchreyes